http://www.engineeringsupplies.co.uk/privacy.html

CollectionsHole MakingLathe ToolsMaterialsMilling ToolsMiscellaneousSpindle ToolingPPE/Safety/WorkwearThreadingWorkshop ToolsClearanceSpecial OffersInformationAbout usDeliveryPrivacy PolicyReturnsTerms & conditionsHome404 PageContact UsPrivacy PolicyThis Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Templeton Tools & Machinery Ltd collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the www.engineeringsupplies.co.uk website ("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Templeton Tools & Machinery Ltd.Personal identification informationWe may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the siteplace, an orderfill out, a formsubscribe to the newsletter and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number,Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously.We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.Non-personal identification informationWe may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilised and other similar information.Web browser cookiesOur Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.How we use collected informationTempleton Tools & Machinery Ltd collects and uses Users personal information for the following purposes: To improve customer service	Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs. To personalise user experience	We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site. To improve our Site	We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you. To process transactions	We may use the information Users provide about themselves when placing an order only to provide service to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service. To administer a content, promotion, survey or other Site feature	To send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them. To send periodic emails 	The email address Users provide for order processing, will only be used to send them information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, and/or other requests or questions. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or User may contact us via our Site.How we protect your informationWe adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorised access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and its Users happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures. Our Site is also in compliance with PCI vulnerability standards in order to create as secure of an environment as possible for Users.Third party websitesUsers may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website\'s own terms and policies.Changes to this privacy policyTempleton Tools & Machinery Ltd has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, revise the updated date at the bottom of this page,. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.Your acceptance of these termsBy using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy and terms of service. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.Contacting usIf you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:Templeton Tools & Machinery Ltdwww.engineeringsupplies.co.ukTempleton Tools,Unit7, Parkburn Court,Parkburn Industrial Estate,Hamilton,ML3 0QQ01698821111sales@engineeringsupplies.co.ukOur Products Hole making Lathe tools Materials Milling tools Misc Ppe/safety/workwear Spindle tooling Threading Workshop toolsCustomer Services About us Delivery Returns Sign In New Account Scrap Carbide Buy Back Privacy policy Terms & conditions Site mapContact Us Contact Us
Tel : 01698 821111
Email: sales@engineeringsupplies.co.uk Follow us on Twitter     © 2020 Engineering Supplies.Open: 9am - 5pmExpert help: 01698 821111Sign In  //   New Account  //   £0.00   View BasketHomeHole MakingSolid DrillsHSS, Cobalt & Powder MetallurgyCarbide DrillsIndexable DrillingU-Drill BodiesCarbide U-Drill InsertsMagnetic DrillingRotabroach CuttersMagnetic Drilling MachinesRotabroach AccessoriesReamingIntermediate Machine Reamers (0.01mm Increments)Standard Machine & Hand ReamersExtra Long Taper Shank Machine ReamersTaper Bridge / Alignment ReamersCar ReamersFloating ReamersCounterbores & CountersinksLathe ToolsTurning Inserts & HoldersExternal ToolholdersInternal Boring BarsCarbide InsertsGrooving & PartingExternal HoldersInternal HoldersFace Grooving HoldersCarbide InsertsMaterialsGauge PlateMetricImperialSilver Steel / Stubbs SteelMetricImperialMilling ToolsSolid Carbide CuttersMastermill VX RangeMastermill AL-HPCHX2 - Multi Helix MillingSabre Roughers/RippersPulsar BluePulsarPulsar DMXALU-XPStandard Carbide K30ALL Solid Carbide Milling CuttersCobalt CuttersIntermediate CuttersForm CuttersApplication Form CuttersIndexable MillingHigh Feed Milling Bodies 15°Face Milling Bodies 45°Shoulder Milling Bodies 90°Profile Milling 0°Modular Indexable HeadsCarbide InsertsmiscCarbide BurrsBandsaw BladesPPE/Safety/WorkwearSpindle ToolingBridgeport UpgradesEASYCHANGE SystemER ColletsER SEALED ColletsER ColletsER Tapping ColletsBack End HoldersBT40 (MAS 403) SystemDV (DIN 69871) SystemDIN2080 (ISO) SystemHSK 63A SystemVDI (DIN69880 / ISO10889)R8 SystemStraight Shank HoldersCentresRevolving Live CentresStatic Dead CentresBoring HeadsBoring HeadsBoring Head HoldersBoring Head Tools & KitsOther Spindle ToolingPull StudsTightening FixturesSpindle Tooling SparesQuick Change Tap AdaptorsBoring Bar SleevesTurret SocketsMTS Sleeves & ExtensionsDrill Chuck ArborsKeyless ChucksThreadingHand TapsCarbon / DIYHSSAccessoriesDiesCarbon / DIYHSSAccessoriesMachine TapsUniversal TapsApplication TapsThread MillingSolid Carbide MillsThread Repair ProductsWire Thread Inserts & KitsThread TurningExternal ToolholdersInternal Thread BarsCarbide InsertsWorkshop ToolsContact
